Guide to the M. Moran Weston Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XVI: Film, Audiotapes and Casettes
  - Archbishop of Canterbury's Sermon, (3 Audio Tapes) (Box 174, Folder 964)
  - Dr. Moran M. Weston Sermons and Speeches, 1963 - 1968, (9 Audio Recording Tapes) (Box 174)
- Series XVII: Miscellaneous
  - Currency and coins of United States Nigeria and Canada, (3 bills, 8 coins) (Box 166, Folder 134A)
  - Resumes, memoranda, letters re. staff., personnel matters (Box 170)
- Series XVIII: Books
  - Printed Material, (3 Books) (Box 165)
- Series XIX: Damaged Files
  This series contains files which were damaged by water and mould. They have been treated and stabilized.
  - 1950 Misson (Box 175, Folder 965)
  - Address to the Diocese of Pennsylvania, 1953 (Box 175, Folder 966)
  - Advent Sunday Sermon, 1954 (Box 175, Folder 967)
  - Correspondence, 1952 & 1953 (Box 175, Folder 968)
  - "Creating a Fit Community for the Children We Care For", 1952 & 1953 (Box 175, Folder 969)
  - E.C. News Editorials (Box 175, Folder 970)
  - Field Trip Reports, 1956 (Box 175, Folder 971)
  - "Forgiveness" (Box 175, Folder 972)
  - Girls' Conference, 1955 (Box 175, Folder 973)
  - "New Occasions Teach Nes Duties" (Box 175, Folder 974)
  - "One World In Christ", 1956, (Sermon) (Box 175, Folder 975)
  - Parish Programs, (2 folders) (Box 175, Folder 976)
  - Possible Articles by M.M.W. (Box 176, Folder 977)
  - Reference Material for Sermons and Speeches, (4 folders) (Box 176, Folder 978 - 981)
  - Sermons, 1950s (Box 177, Folder 982)
  - Sermons In-Process (Box 177, Folder 983)
  - Completed Sermons, 1951 (Box 177, Folder 984)
  - Sermons and speeches, (6 folders) (Box 177, Folder 985 - 990)
  - Notes for Sermons and speeches, (5 folders) (Box 178, Folder 991 - 995)
  - "Setting Your Heart On The Right Things" (Box 178, Folder 996)
  - Speeches (Box 178, Folder 997)
  - Text of Addresses, 1956 (Box 178, Folder 998)
  - "Time For Revival" (Box 178, Folder 999)